Thanks for giving my bike a spring tune-up, Parker.
No problem, munch.
I wanna make sure the thing that carries you
away from here is working at all times.
All right, boys, clear out.
Varsity softball tryouts are coming up, and I need the backyard to practice.
Forget it, Maddie. We were here first.
Hi, Joey.
Oh, dear.
Backyard is all yours, Maddie.
No, I wasn't finished!
- (Screams) - (Crashes)
The backyard's all yours, Maddie.
(Theme music plays)
Better in stereo
b... b... better in stereo
-   I'm up with the sunshine  -   Let's go
-   I lace up my high tops  -   Oh no
-   slam dunk  -   Ready or not
yeah, show me what you got
I'm under the spotlight   Holler
I dare you, come on and follow
you dance to your own beat
I'll sing the melody
when you say yea-ah-ah
I say no-oh-oh
when you say stop
all I want to do is go, go, go
you, you, the other half of me, me
the half I'll never be-e
the half that drives me crazy
you, you, the better half of me, me
the half I'll always need
but we both know
we're better in stereo.
(SIGHS)
It's here! It's here.
My future is here.
My future is here!
Between two slices of bread.
Your future can wait.
Look.
That's the costume from "space werewolves."
"Space werewolves" is a big action blockbuster
that's gonna be kind of like the next "twilight,"
except it's werewolves in space instead of vampires on earth.
It's way more believable.
So, you got the lead in the movie.
No. They actually don't think a girl will look tough enough.
So you stole the suit
so they can't make the movie.
You are diabolical.
Actually, I talked them into sending me the werewolf suit
so I can take pictures in it to prove them wrong.
That could work too.
I like you better diabolical.
(Chuckles)
Liv, great news.
Channel four just called.
They're coming to the house this Friday
to interview you
for their morning news cooking segment.
I'm doing "nibbling with nimbus"?
Yes. Can you believe it?
I love that segment.
Last week, nimbus deep fried a Turkey with VIN diesel.
Wait, mom, did you say Friday?
So a "space werewolves" movie photo shoot
and a live TV interview.
(Chuckles)
Okay, this is shaping up to be an oddly stressful week.
Well, luckily you have a super-cool mom
who's also a therapist. And she can help you manage your stress.
Good. Because I am going to need your help
picking out a TV-rrific outfit.
You want my fashion advice.
Oh, it's finally happening.
Okay.
How about a peasant blouse
with some sensible trousers?
Yeah, this was a mistake.
Green belts, the path of the dragon
is not easy.
Hyah!
Do not be scared.
The fly lives, barely.
(Fly buzzes)
But only so he can warn his friends
that distractions will not be tolerated.
Wow, sensei rae dawn is no joke.
I heard if you look directly in her eyes,
she can steal your soul.
Dragon Parker,
are you ready to advance from green belt
to blue belt
by unleashing your inner dragon
and performing the leaping dragon back-kick?
(Exhales) Ready, sensei.
Hyah!
(Cheers)
Impressive, young dragon.
Your belt.
Remind your parents it's 9.95 for the new belt
and 1.20 for the target you broke.
Dragon Evan,
- are you ready... - Let me stop you right there.
My mom says I can't unleash my dragon today.
Excuse me?
She thinks I shouldn't participate in an activity
where kids are judged in terms of winning or failing.
Especially when I'm going to fail.
Anyway I can get a blue belt
by being open about my feelings
and talking out issues?
Seems your inner dragon is more of a salamander.
No belt for you.
You have one week to earn your blue belt
or endure the shame of watching the rest of the class
move on to the 2:30 Tuesday slot
without you.
There was no way I was gonna let the sensei
break up the team of
super-awesome martial arts dude
and his beloved sidekick,
freckles, the smiling salamander.
Yeah.
Evan might need a new nickname.
Okay, Willow, ready?
Focus. Fire one at me. Right here.
Perfect...
If we were playing "smash that pot."
Willow, you've been in a slump for days.
I just can't concentrate.
Okay, well, softball tryouts are this weekend,
and if we want to be the first sophomores to make varsity,
then you gotta get your head in the game.
What is your problem?
You know what? I just don't feel comfortable
talking about it.
Okay, well, we have to get to the bottom
of whatever this is before tryouts.
And if you're not willing to talk to me,
then maybe we need some professional help.
(Gasps) Did someone say "professional help"?
(Pants)
It is finally happening.
Thank you for seeing me in my office.
Thank you for the ride.
Well, I thought we would be more comfortable here.
And I thought you'd be more receptive to my words
if you could see all my degrees.
So, Willow can't pitch.
Exactly. Fix her.
So you tell me what is the first thing
that pops into your head.
Joey.
Joey on a horse that looks like Joey.
Okay.
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
and say that this has something
to do with Joey.
Wow, you're good.
(Scoffs) Joey?
This whole thing is about Joey?
Maddie, this is a safe place.
We do not judge,
even if it is the first place
your brain wants to go.
Okay, so what is going on with you and Joey?
Nothing. That's the problem.
It's springtime.
Love is in the air, birds are chirping,
but all I can think about is
why doesn't my sweet little Joey bird chirp at me?
Okay, what... what does Joey have to do with your pitching?
I can't concentrate.
When I pitch, I look directly at you.
- Right. - But every time I look at you,
all I see is Joey.
I look like Joey?! No, okay.
(Clears throat) We both wear glasses,
but that is where the similarity ends, right?
Right?!
So the reason you stink at pitching
is because of me?
Yeah. You guys look exactly like each other.
Except he makes it work.
Oh, good, you're here. I really need to talk.
Oh, I'm all ears.
(Chuckles)
Okay, Willow's in a slump and she can't pitch,
and that's gonna keep her from making varsity softball.
(Groans) Sports.
(Groans)
But the reason she can't pitch
is because she can't concentrate on anything
other than her massive crush on Joey.
Ooh, feelings. Yay.
Willow's just so awesome,
and I wish she would realize that there's so much more out there
in the world for her other than just Joey.
Okay, so make her see that there's more out there.
(Gasps) Put a love note from a secret admirer
in her locker, and she'll forget all about Joey.
Liv, that's actually a really good idea.
Actually, I remember in fourth grade
when I was so obsessed with marky Stevens
that I literally couldn't even play kickball.
And then I got a secret admirer note from...
You.
And who went on to win top prize
in the school kickball-y thing?
Uh-huh, you're welcome.
- Whatcha doing? - Ooh!
Do not sneak up on me like that.
What are you doing at Willow's locker?
More importantly, what am I doing at Willow's locker?
Is that a note?
Yeah, actually, don't tell anyone,
but I'm doing us both a favor.
It's a secret admirer note
to get Willow to stop obsessing about you.
I hope you wrote a good one.
Willow's got a bad case of the Joeys,
and I'm not sure there's a cure.
Hmm, the hairs on the back of my neck just stood up.
Willow's coming. Run.
Hey, Joey.
(Imitating Joey) Hey, beautiful.
(Normal voice) What's this?
Secret admirer?
Oh-ho. No way.
It looks like she's buying it.
(Chuckles)
Stop standing like me.
We do not look alike.
Evan, I know you're disappointed
that you didn't get your blue belt.
Actually, I'm cool.
I've accepted it as a part of life's journey.
Come on, Evan. We're a team.
That can't be how you really feel.
You're right. My mom told me to say that.
You wouldn't believe the things I've accepted
as part of life's journey.
But I really do want my blue belt.
Then we've got to unleash your inner dragon.
You heard the sensei.
If you don't become a blue belt
by our next class, we move on without you.
Hey, just because I stink
doesn't mean I don't understand English.
We are gonna get you angry enough
to release all your pent up inner aggression.
This is the new balance plate lunchbox
your mom made you get, right?
But didn't you want the cool ufc lunchbox
with the dude's eyeball falling out?
My mom thought it was too violent.
Plus, this one had a carrot thermos.
Evan, if you want that cool ufc lunchbox,
you need to smash the balance plate.
Come on, dude. Reach down deep and breathe some fire.
(Exhales)
You know, I better not.
Mom says if I don't bring it home,
I don't get my dessert.
And you know how I love raw almonds.
Liv, you ready for your "space werewolves" photo shoot?
Stand back, humanoid, or feel my fury.
(Hisses)
Whoa. You look awesome.
(Squeals) Thanks, dad.
(Giggles) Now let's do this.
- Snarl. - (Snarls)
-  Growl. - (Growls)
- Howl. - (Howls)
Show me fierce.
Boom, pow, Wha-cha!
No!
Dad, the armor glue they sent me
said it's supposed to be permanent.
Don't worry. I got some fantastic shots
before your suit fell apart.
Oh, great. That one's perfect.
Now I can take these itchy ears off.
(Chuckles) Ow.
(Chuckles) They're stuck.
Oh, okay. So are my fangs.
That's so weird.
The makeup glue that they sent me
says it's only supposed to last 20 minutes.
And the armor glue says "permanent."
Hey, mads.
What a beautiful day.
I see heart shapes in the clouds,
and the air smells like Jasmine and hot dogs.
I got a note from a secret admirer.
- You did? - (Both squeal)
(Clears throat)
Wow, that's totally unlike us.
Yeah, let's please never do that again.
But I can't really say I'm surprised.
You are a top-notch lady
who any guy would be lucky to have.
Now let's get us on that varsity squad.
Turn my hand into a bloody pulp.
My secret admirer is Joey Rooney.
My little Joey bird finally chirped back!
Wait, Joey?
There was nothing in that note about Joey...
I'm assuming because you said it was a secret.
For the first time in weeks,
my mind is clear and I can concentrate.
I mean, it's obviously Joey, right?
(Chuckles nervously)
Okay, so I know I should have come clean
right then and there to protect my brother
and my best friend, but in my defense...
Yeah, okay. I got nothing.
Sure. Yeah.
Why not? (Nervous chuckle)
The point is that you are out of your slump
and now we can get you ready for tryouts.
Yeah, about that.
I'm quitting softball.
What?!
Willow, you can't.
Relationships take work.
This thing I have going on with Joey
has to be my top priority.
See you later, mads,
if I ever come back down to earth.
Wow.
There really is no cure for a bad case of the Joeys.
Young dragons, before we give the weak link
known as Evan his final chance
to earn his blue belt,
take a few moments to feed your inner dragons.
It's snack time. Work with me here.
I was about to give up and look for a new sidekick
when I remembered the time Evan lost it
because his mom gave him seaweed chips.
So I swapped out his raw almonds
for some of that disgusting water weed.
At least we get to have snack together one last time.
Are you ready for your snack?
You should have your snack.
- I'm not really that... - I said eat your snack.
I can't believe this!
What's wrong?
It's seaweed chips!
Unsalted, organic, seaweed chips.
I keep telling my mom I hate them.
Give me carrot sticks or celery
or even rutabaga, just not seaweed chips!
Come on, dude.
Listen to your mom and eat it!
I won't eat seaweed!
(Shouts)
(Yells)
(Grunts)
What, what?!
(Shouts, grunts continue)
(Screams)
(Gasping)
I'm a good friend.
Who else wants some?
Dragon Evan, that was your inner dragon.
It's been released!
You are ready for your blue belt now.
Yes! Evan, you did it.
Tell me something that I don't know.
Try to keep up, munch.
Good morning, Stevens point.
And welcome to "nibblin' with nimbus"
where every week, Wisconsin's favorite meteorologist...
this guy... cooks up some breakfast
for one of Stevens point's most intriguing residents or visitors.
And this week, we got a tasty combination
of breakfast brats
and the always flavorful star
of "sing it loud," Liv Rooney.
I tried all night
to get my ears and my fangs off.
They wouldn't budge. I tried cancelling
and Johnny nimbus showed up anyway.
So I did what any great actress would do.
I hid my flaws with wardrobe and props.
Live and in person, here she is now.
Wow, Liv Rooney, that is a nice getup.
Tell me, is that what all the kids are wearing these days?
'Cause if not, they will be after watching this.
Ah, who am I kidding?
No kids are watching this program.
Johnny, you are adorable.
So tell us, what are you cooking up this morning?
Well, I got a griddle full of brats
and a side order of get to know you.
Huh? (Chuckles)
Okay, now these eggs are ready for poaching.
And here's a secret I learned from Nana nimbus.
Don't use water. Use chicken broth instead.
Liv Rooney, could you open that for me.
- Mm-hmm. - All right.
(Chuckles)
(Bites, can crunches)
Here you go, Johnny.
Wow! That was quick.
All right. Now get poaching.
There you go.
Just liberally putting it in there.
They're gonna taste great.
Okay. Now.
Let's sit down to chew the fat.
And I mean that literally.
These brats are 90% fat.
Well, come on, Liv.
Come on over and sink your teeth
into one of these babies.
Oopsie-Daisy.
Oh, Liv, here. Let me help you up.
Here... oh!
Either I've had too much coffee,
or werewolves are real!
Um... (Chuckles)
Uh, no. Actually, Johnny,
I am just giving you a channel four exclusive.
I am up for the lead in "space werewolves,"
so to get my fans excited,
I decided that I would give you a little sneak peek.
- (Growls) - Oh!
Seriously.
You're kind of freaking me out.
Hey, did Willow get the note?
- Yeah, she did, but... - Was she happy?
Well, yeah, she was... shh shh shh shh.
All I needed to know is that she's off my scent.
You have served your purpose.
Hey, Willow.
Willow Willow Willow.
I heard you got a little note in your locker.
I did.
I bet you're pretty excited about that, huh?
I say chase this rainbow and see where it takes you.
- Um, Joey... - Maddie.
Not now.
I've been waiting for this moment
for a long time.
I just can't take it anymore.
Joey Rooney's my secret admirer!
What is happening?
Yeah.
Uh, I think it's best that the three of us
talk about this in a safe place.
Willow.
You can put him down now.
Oh, I didn't realize.
It just feels so right.
(SIGHS) Thank you.
Punish Maddie, mom.
Make her clean the bathrooms for the next five years.
Yeah, punish her.
Your bathrooms could use a little help.
There are six of us living in one house.
I do the best I can.
Maddie, what I'm hearing
is that your brother and your overly critical best friend
are understandably upset.
Willow, I was really just trying to help.
I didn't want to see my best friend
drive herself crazy over some stupid guy.
Um... The stupid guy is right here.
Thanks, Maddie, but you shouldn't have interfered.
I know.
And I'm sorry.
But you're a great girl
who  so  does not need a guy to make her feel better about herself.
Never forget that.
You're not really quitting softball, are you?
No, you're right.
- We're making varsity. - (Grunts)
I shouldn't get hung up on what some stupid guy thinks.
Again, right here.
So Maddie, is there anything you would like to say to your brother?
Yeah. Joey...
Did you eat the last muffin this morning?
Maddie.
(SIGHS)
Uh... I should not have let
Willow think that you were her secret admirer.
Exactly.
How Willow and I feel about each other
is none of your business.
- (Gasps) - Oh, no.
Joey just said he and I had feelings...
About each other.
(Giggles)
Um, no.
What I meant was... I'm going now.
And Maddie, I did eat that muffin.
(Panting)
Hide me!
I unleashed Evan's inner dragon
and now I can't put it back in its cage.
(Shouts)
Where's Parker?
My dragon wants to throw him around some more.
No idea what you're talking about, son.
Don't lie to me, old man.
I can see him trembling behind you.
What did I say about running in the house?
What did I say about talking back, woman?
(Squeals)
Stop, drop and howl.
Dad, the "space werewolves" movie people called,
and apparently my video went viral.
And the only thing they love more than all the free publicity
were all the free pics you took.
I'm back on the short list for the lead.
I'm so proud of my little werewolf.
Aah!
Cage your dragon! Cage your dragon!
(Growls)
Hi, Evan.
(Screams)
Oh, right. (Chuckles)